Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

#### Who We Are

Our website address is [https://qbs.com](https://qbs.com/ "QBS").

#### What Personal Data We Collect & Why We Collect It

_Comments_

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: [https://automattic.com/privacy/](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### Contact Forms – Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address, and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### Embedded Content from Other Websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Analytics – How Long We Retain Your Data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profiles. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

#### What Rights You Have Over Your Data

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

#### Where We Send Your Data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### Interested in Switching to Safety-Care?

Read the 12 reasons to adopt Safety-Care Crisis Prevention Training

Let’s Connect
-------------

Interested in learning more about our evidence-based, behavior management and crisis intervention training programs?

We’d love to learn about your organization’s unique challenges and needs. Simply fill out the form with your information, and a member of our team will be in touch.

How Can We Help You?
--------------------

Name \* 

Email \* 

Phone \* 

Subject \* 

How can we help your organization? \*

Organization Name \* 

Organization State / Province \* \--None--Alabama Alaska Alberta Arizona Arkansas British Columbia California Colorado Connecticut Delaware Devonshire District of Columbia Federal District Florida Georgia Hamilton Hawaii Idaho Illinois Indiana Iowa Kansas Kentucky Louisiana Maine Manitoba Maryland Massachusetts Michigan Minnesota Mississippi Missouri Montana Nebraska Nevada New Brunswick Newfoundland and Labrador New Hampshire New Jersey New Mexico New York North Carolina North Dakota Northwest Territories Nova Scotia Nunavut Ohio Oklahoma Ontario Oregon Paget Pembroke Pennsylvania Prince Edward Island Puerto Rico Quebec Rhode Island Sandys Saskatchewan Smiths Southampton South Carolina South Dakota St Georges Tennessee Texas Utah Vermont Virginia Warwick Washington West Virginia Wisconsin Wyoming Yukon Territories

Are you currently a Safety-Care Customer? \* \--None--Yes, my organization uses Safety Care No, we do not currently use Safety Care

Industry \* \--None--Agriculture Apparel Banking Biotechnology Chemicals Communications Construction Consulting Education Electronics Emergency Services Energy Engineering Entertainment Environmental Finance Food & Beverage Government Healthcare Hospitality Insurance Machinery Manufacturing Media Not For Profit Other Recreation Retail Shipping Technology Telecommunications Transportation Utilities

Subscribe to Newsletter

 Yes

49 Plain St, Suite #200,

North Attleboro, MA 02760

Phone: [855-727-6246](tel:855-727-6246)

Fax: [508-316-4274](tel:508-316-4274)

Email: [info@qbs.com](mailto:info@qbs.com)

#### Quick Links

### Follow Us:

### QBS Newsletter

Stay up to date with all of QBS’s behavioral news & updates

I would like to receive the QBS Newsletter

You can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the link in the footer of our emails. Form more information, please visit our privacy policy.

Please leave this field empty.

Δ

© 2022 QBS LLC. All Rights Reserved. | [Privacy Policy](https://qbs.com/privacy-policy) | [Terms & Conditions](https://qbs.com/terms-and-conditions/) | [W-9 Form](https://qbs.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/W9-QBS-LLC-2024.pdf) | [Sole Source](https://qbs.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Sole-Source-Letter-2024.pdf)
